🎮 Pat's Game Collection
A collection of 8 mini‑games and tools built in Python — from a cafe system to a secure message encryptor.

Perfect for learning Python basics, error handling, logging, and file I/O.

🚀 Games & Tools
#	Name	Description

1	Age Checker	Calculates your age from birth year. Handles future years and unrealistic ages.
2	Calculator	Basic arithmetic with division‑by‑zero protection.
3	Cafe System	Order food with quantity limits and price calculation.
4	Guessing Game	Guess a number (1‑3) to reach 3 points. Wrong answers cost a point!
5	Big Text Search	Find a word in a large block of text. Warns about very long inputs.
6	Rock‑Paper‑Scissors	Best‑of‑3 against the computer. Play again option.
7	Encrypt / Decrypt	Secure message encryption with Fernet. Save keys and messages to a file.
8	Random Picker Wheel	Build a custom list and let the computer pick random items.

📦 Requirements
Python 3.6 or higher

Optional (but recommended):

cryptography – for encryption features
cowsay – for the farewell cow

Install optional modules:
bash
pip install -r requirements.txt
💡 If a module is missing, the game will still run – only the affected feature will be disabled.

🛡️ Error Handling
The game is designed to be crash‑proof:

✅ All user inputs are validated

✅ Division by zero is caught

✅ Missing modules are handled gracefully

✅ File write errors are caught

✅ Any unexpected error is logged to game.log

🧠 What You'll Learn
Concept	Where it appears
Functions	Every game is its own function
Loops	while True with break conditions
Conditionals	Game rules, menu choices
Error handling	try/except everywhere
Logging	All actions and errors are logged
File I/O	Saving encrypted data
Modules	random, datetime, os, logging, cryptography, cowsay

📝 Logging
All game events are logged to game.log in the same folder:

User actions

Scores

Errors

Warnings

Check it if something unexpected happens!

🐮 Farewell Cow
At the end, a cow says something you choose (if cowsay is installed).
If you type nothing, it says "Moo!" by default.

🙌 Credits
Built by Patrick as a practice project.
